Ok.  The quantity you have is 900 and the
entry price is 1800.  Ok?
Ok.  Let's take some advice on this.
Ajit ji, he has ICICI Lombard.  He has
bought 900 shares, he has a long term view at the price of 1800
and the current price is
1823.  I think he
bought them around this time.
He bought it around this time.  What
will be your perspective?
Look, no doubt, Validity has a lot of experience in the insurance space
across life insurance and general
insurance counters but ICICI GI has a
comparatively better structure.  Meaning, you
saw a retracement from the record high,
from around 2200 you came to the levels of 1680 and as far as
I can see,
in the last one and a quarter years, you are seeing trading in the same band from 2000 to 1600
because their buying price is
near the current levels.  There is a long term view.
I think it should remain that way.  As of now the
1600 level is holding.  Till now
no major damage is visible
in the structure.  The overall consolidation will
remain with a positive bias.  The actual growth will happen
around 2050.  In that case,
you will again see the stock moving towards a new high.
So right now the opinion would be to hold
for long term with a stop loss of 1600.
You have to hold for now with a stop loss of 1600.
You are getting this opinion.
Let's move ahead.  Another caller has now
joined us.  Himanshu is associated with us.
Himanshu, welcome to your home country.
Hi, tell me which stock do you want advice on
?
Sir,
how many shares do you have in SML Mahindra?   I have
10 shares.
Good sir.  It is priced at Rs 4200.
Yes sir.  Yes sir.
Ok.  How many days can you keep it?   There is
no problem for a month or two.   A
month or two.  Ok?  So short term
is the only perspective.  Ajit ji, he has
shares of SML Mahindra.  There are 10 shares.  He has bought it at the price of Rs 4200.
Running around 3800.  A
correction of around 10% has already
come from where they bought.  And
even today the stock is trading 5% down.  The
results that came were not good.  The
streets did not like it well.
What is your stance?  What do you say?  What
should they do?  This is a one or two month perspective.
Absolutely, if you look at the development,
you will see a very strong bullish trend, like the rally that you saw from 1000 to 5000
in the stock, now for the
last four months we are seeing
that this tone of consolidation has come in the stock
and if it breaks the level of 3700, then
according to me your short term bias will
change from positive to
sideways and maybe even negative, so according to me
they should not continue the long position below 3700
because they have a
view of one to two months and
in the above case, you may see this stock rising at one time from 4200 to 4400 which is their
buying price zone.
So, you'll find it roughly in the
range of 3700 to [nasal sound] 4400.
So until there is a
decisive close
above the upper band, there is no indication of any significant momentum here.
So it would be better that if
any recovery comes then utilize it
to reduce the position and at the same time
maintain a stop loss of Rs 3700.
Ok?  You must maintain a stop loss of Rs 3700 on
this.  This advice is being given to you Himanshu ji.